{
    "subject": "resource/Clark_Haggans",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Colorado_State_Rams_football_players",
    "human_readable": "Clark Haggans is about Colorado State Rams football players.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.72995924949646,
            "question": "Who is Clark Haggans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615795493125916,
            "question": "What team is Clark Haggans associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557300686836243,
            "question": "Is Clark Haggans a current player?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6137254238128662,
            "question": "What position did Clark Haggans play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.594548225402832,
            "question": "What sport does Clark Haggans play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.584604024887085,
            "question": "What are some key moments in Clark Haggans' football career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5406193137168884,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements associated with Clark Haggans?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.514360249042511,
            "question": "When was Clark Haggans most active in football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4118766784667969,
            "question": "Is Clark Haggans known for a specific playing style or skill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2292349636554718,
            "question": "Has Clark Haggans been inducted into any halls of fame?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clark Haggans is about Colorado State Rams football players.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1497_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Clark Haggans known for a specific playing style or skill?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1497_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Clark Haggans most active in football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1497_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable achievements associated with Clark Haggans?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1497_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1497_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Clark Haggans played college football for the Colorado State University, specifically the Rams, as mentioned in several documents (63.txt, 79.txt, 89.txt, and others)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information supporting that Clark Haggans was a football player for the Colorado State Rams during his college years and had a significant impact on the program, including leading the team in total sacks. This supports the statement that he is associated with Colorado State Rams football players."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}